Have you insured your two-wheeler worth Rs. 1 lakh or
not? Have you
insured your vehicle worth Rs. 10 lakh or
not? Because it has become
mandatory but what have
you done for your priceless health?
Life is unpredictable. Health is not
always in our hands. When
illnesses come, it is
often difficult to afford the treatment costs.
That is when
we understand the importance of health insurance.   You will not have to
suffer financially when you get sick.  If you are
insured, you can also avail 100% cashless and unlimited package under the new plan called Elevate from ICICI Long Bar
General Insurance. In addition to
this plan, you will also get attractive discounts of up to 15% if you are civil score eligible, 25% if you have NRI status, and if you choose multiple years.
Get insured today and protect your health. For
more information, contact this number
[Music]